Dad!
Zihao.
Shoot. Kill him.
Dad.
Don't force me.
Shoot.
Shoot!
Xie Zihao.
Drop the gun.
Xie Guanhong.
Let him go.
Dad...
Dad!
I...
Shoot.
It's so simple.
Kill him.
I'll go with you.
You can't kill anyone else, Dad.
Zihao!
Zihao, don't!
Don't!
Liang Zhiqiang is your real father!
Kill him!
Run!
Go!
Zihao!
Run!
Xie Guanhong!
Go!
Zihao!
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Zihao?
Stop!
Don't run!
On my turf,
you want to fight me?
You can't beat me.
Xie Guanhong, you're not human!
Yeah.
I'm not human!
You're not human!
Are you even human?!
You...
You murderer!
I'm a murderer!
I've killed so many people.
I have nightmares every night.
Kill me.
Avenge them!
I'm a murderer.
I'm beyond redemption.
I'm a monster.
Kill me.
Kill me!
A Qiang.
You've already done twenty years.
If you go back in,
you'll never get out.
You can't kill him.
Kill me.
We'll become monsters together.
Come on, Liang Zhiqiang!
Shut the hell up!
Come on, kill me!
Don't!
What are you doing?
Why didn't you kill me?
All my life,
my favorite thing was going out to fight.
Fighting to see who was more ruthless.
To see who could
be the last one standing.
For twenty years,
it's always been like this.
If you're not ruthless enough,
then you just die.
I kill people,
people kill me.
It's completely normal.
I hold no grudges.
And I have no regrets.
But in my entire life,
there is only one person
I feel I've let down.
I feel like
I owe him.
That person is you,
Liang Zhiqiang.
Little Qiang.
Sometimes I really miss
when we were kids.
To be honest,
we were all there.
We took a boat from the fishing village
and came here.
I really never thought
things would end up like this.
The second Operation Portland Street was a massive success.
Harbor City and mainland police launched a joint strike,
successfully dismantling the United Righteous Group,
a criminal syndicate, formerly a triad.
They successfully solved
the case of the female teacher's fatal fall
and several other major crimes.
A series of gang-related violent incidents,
including illegal loan sharks,
forced prostitution, captivity, extortion,
have all seen massive breakthroughs.
Most notably,
the police made a rare public disclosure
that members of the force are suspected of
shielding triad organizations.
Several police officers have been formally
charged by the Independent Commission Against Corruption.
What a big fish.
It took the bait.
Let's go.
Mainland police officials also spoke,
vowing to uphold Harbor City's stability,
and thoroughly eradicate criminal forces.
They stated mutual cooperation will deepen
to jointly safeguard law and order.
Good work.
Thank you, Sir.
Come on.
This shop has been open for a long time.
Now it's being torn down.
It's good they're tearing it down.
Old things
should be torn down to build new ones.
Thanks.
We're leaving Harbor City.
I applied to schools abroad for Zihao.
Once we get there,
I'll find a job after we settle in.
Don't worry.
Take care.
All the best.
Take care of yourself.
And take care of your mom.
One day,
I'll take back what I lost
with my own hands.
Little Qiang.
Uncle told us to go move the fish.
Okay, coming!